module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'Who said: "Who likes nuts in their pie?"', 
    a: 'Mercan',
    b: 'Jane',
    c: 'JoCo',
    d: 'Adam',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who said: "I\'m going to give you so many holes for this."', 
    a: 'Billy',
    b: 'JoCo',
    c: 'Jane',
    d: 'RA',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who said: "But seriously, I don\'t trust the government."', 
    a: 'Marion',
    b: 'Jane',
    c: 'Joshua',
    d: 'RG',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who said: "Why are all these chips mad exotic?"', 
    a: 'Erica',
    b: 'BDF',
    c: 'Dante',
    d: 'Chels-B',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who said to West: "Do you have siblings? God, I bet you would be so annoying."', 
    a: 'Marisa',
    b: 'Shannon',
    c: 'Kevin',
    d: 'Troy',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who said: "It\'s like airbnb, for your body."', 
    a: 'Dante',
    b: 'Mercan',
    c: 'Troy',
    d: 'Cahak',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who said: "An alternate name for a hotdog is a tubesteak."', 
    a: 'Jane',
    b: 'JoCo',
    c: 'Dante',
    d: 'Mercan',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who said: "I\'m more of a penguin. Slow and dumb, but cute."', 
    a: 'Troy',
    b: 'JoCo',
    c: 'Shanwow',
    d: 'Tomi',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who said to an interview candidate: "Pricey Comfort? That would be my stripper name."', 
    a: 'JoCo',
    b: 'Jane',
    c: 'Mike',
    d: 'Dante',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who said: "It\'s just like, we farted... but now there was a microphone next to it."', 
    a: 'Shannon',
    b: 'Mike',
    c: 'Ashley',
    d: 'RG',
    answer: 'b'
  },
];